tamilmoviegallery.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer - Tamil Movie Gallery

You are here: [Home](http://www.tamilmoviegallery.com/) » Privacy Policy & Disclaimer

[](http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-85VcsqhJTz8/UCO6H4as6fI/AAAAAAAAUSY/ASeNJu0nziQ/s1600/TMG-07+\(Custom\).jpg)  
---  
  
**  
****Privacy Policy**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.  
Sites like Google AdSense, Google Analytics, FeedBurner, Ozonemedia or other third-party services may place and read cookies or use web beacons to collect non-personal information. These services use the data to track conversions, to show statistics about this site or to improve their features.  
Cookies are small pieces of data that reside on your computer and can only be read by the sites that placed them. You can disable cookies, manually clear them and control which cookies are allowed.  
To find more, read Google’s privacy policy, Yahoo’s privacy policy and the privacy policies of the third-party services accepted by Google AdSense.  
The ads from this site are served by Google AdSense, a third-party service that shows contextually-targeted ads, placement-targeted ads and interested-based ads. Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie to serve ads based on the sites you have recently visited. You can go to the Google Ads Preferences page to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie.  
**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or concerns please contact - _ _   _sridhar@_ **tamilmoviegallery.com**  
This privacy policy updated March 2013.

 **Disclaimer**

Some images contained in moviegalleri.net have been obtained from various internet sources. The copyright of these pictures belongs to their original publisher / photographer. Please let us know at if any Copyright Violation occurs and we will remove them right away. If by anyhow any of the content is offensive to you, please, contact us asking for the removal. If you own copyrights over any of them and do not agree with it being shown here, please send us an email with ownership proof and we will remove it. email us at  _sridhar@_ **tamilmoviegallery.com**

Any links provided or advertisements displayed on our site are for informational purposes only and we are not responsible for any damages or consequences. However, if you find any unsuitable link / advertisement, then please contact us giving detail of such links etc.

 _Webmaster_

 __ **www.tamilmoviegallery.com**

Rating: 0.0/ **5** (0 votes cast)
